<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<xliff version="1.1" xmlns="urn:oasis:names:tc:xliff:document:1.1">
	<file source-language="en-US" target-language="it-IT" datatype="po" original="en-US/template.xliff">
		<body>
			<trans-unit id="email.verify.subject">
				<source>@@PRODUCT_NAME@@ login Email Verification</source>
				<target>Verifica email di login di @@PRODUCT_NAME@@</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.verify.body">
				<source>Dear @@PRODUCT_NAME@@ User,

This email is sent to validate the email address that you have
provided for your Red Hat login. Your Red Hat login, in combination
with an active Red Hat subscription, provides you with access to
systems management capabilities through @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.

To ensure the security of the account information associated with your
Red Hat login, please take a moment to click the link below
and verify that we have the correct email address. If you do not
confirm your email address, your Red Hat login will eventually be
deactivated.

To confirm your email address, please visit the following URL:

{0}

Thank you for using @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.
{1}

{2}</source>
				<target>Egregio utente di @@PRODUCT_NAME@@,

Questa email è stata inviata per convalidare l'indirizzo email per
 il suo login di Red Hat. Il suddetto login, in combinazione con una
 sottoscrizione attiva di Red Hat, fornisce un accesso alle capacità
 di gestione dei sistemi attraverso il @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.

Per garantire la sicurezza delle informazioni relative all'account associate con il suo login
di Red Hat, le suggeriamo di spendere qualche secondo per navigare attraverso
 il link di seguito riportato, e di verificare la correttezza dell'indirizzo email. Non
 confermando il suo indirizzo email,  il login di Red Hat potrebbe essere
disabilitato.

Per confermare il suddetto indirizzo email, consultare il seguente URL:

{0}

Grazie per aver usato @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.
{1}

{2}</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.newaccount.subject">
				<source>Your @@PRODUCT_NAME@@ Account is ready</source>
				<target>Il @@PRODUCT_NAME@@ Account è pronto</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.newaccountbycreator.body">
				<source>Hello,

A Red Hat login has been created for you by {0} {1}. Your
Red Hat login, in combination with an active Red Hat subscription,
provides you with access to manage systems on @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.

  Red Hat login: {2}
       Password: {3}
         e-mail: {4}

  {5}

Important: Please change your password upon logging in.

Thank you for using @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.
{6}</source>
				<target>Salve,

Un login di Red Hat è stato appena creato per Lei da {0} {1}. Il
 suddetto login,in combinazione con una sottoscrizione attiva di Red Hat,
 le garantisce la possibilità di gestire i sistemi presenti su @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.

Login di Red Hat: {2}
       Password: {3}
         e-mail: {4}

  {5}

Importante: Si prega di cambiare la password dopo aver eseguito il login.

Grazie per aver usato @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.
{6}</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.newaccount.body">
				<source>Hello,

A Red Hat login has been created for you. Your
Red Hat login, in combination with an active Red Hat subscription,
provides you with access to manage systems on @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.

  Red Hat login: {0}
       Password: {1}
         e-mail: {2}

  {3}

Important: Please change your password upon logging in.

Thank you for using @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.
{4}</source>
				<target>Salve,

Un login di Red Hat è stato appena creato per Lei. Il
 suddetto login,in combinazione con una sottoscrizione attiva di Red Hat,
 le garantisce la possibilità di gestire i sistemi presenti su @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.

Login di Red Hat: {0}
       Password: {1}
         e-mail: {2}

  {3}

Importante: Si prega di cambiare la password dopo aver eseguito il login.

Grazie per aver usato @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.
{4}</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.newaccount.pam.body">
				<source>Hello,

A Red Hat login has been created for you by {0} {1}.  Your
Red Hat login, in combination with an active Red Hat subscription,
provides you with access to manage systems on @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.

  Red Hat login: {2}
         e-mail: {4}

  {5}

Thank you for using @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.
{6}</source>
				<target>Salve,

Un login di Red Hat è stato appena creato per Lei da {0} {1}. Il
suddetto login,in combinazione con una sottoscrizione attiva di Red Hat,
le garantisce la possibilità di gestire i sistemi presenti su @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.

 Login di Red Hat: {2}
         e-mail: {4}

  {5}

 Grazie per aver usato @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.
{6}</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.newuser.subject">
				<source>@@PRODUCT_NAME@@ User Created: {0} ({1}, {2} &lt;{3}&gt;)</source>
				<target>Utente di @@PRODUCT_NAME@@ Creato: {0} ({1}, {2} &lt;{3}&gt;)</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.newuser.body">
				<source>Hello,

A new user has been added to your account.

{0}

To see all the active users and Red Hat logins associated with your account,
please visit:

  {1}

Thank you for using @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.
{2}</source>
				<target>Salve,

Un nuovo utente è stato appena aggiunto al vostro account.

{0}

Per poter visualizzare tutti gli utenti attivi ed i login di Red Hat associati al vostro
 account,
 visitare:

  {1}

Grazie per aver utilizzato @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.
{2}</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.user.deleted.subject">
				<source>@@PRODUCT_NAME@@ Account Deactivated: {0}</source>
				<target>Account @@PRODUCT_NAME@@ disattivato: {0}</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.user.deleted.body">
				<source>
The Red Hat login {0} has been deactivated in response to your request.

Thank you for contacting Red Hat.</source>
				<target>
Il login di Red Hat {0} è stato disattivato a causa della vostra richiesta.

Grazie per aver contattato Red Hat.</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.newuser.bala.subject">
				<source>Red Hat login creation request</source>
				<target>Richiesta creazione login di Red Hat</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.newuser.bala.footer">
				<source>
For additional information in German language, please visit our Website:
{0}</source>
				<target>
Per maggiori informazioni in lingua tedesca vi preghiamo di consultare il nostro sito web:
{0}</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.newuser.bala.footer2">
				<source>
For French, click here: {0}</source>
				<target>
Per il francese, fate clic qui: {0}</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.newuser.bala.body">
				<source>
Dear Red Hat Customer,

You were recently named on an order for new Red Hat subscriptions.  These
subscriptions are now available in the following account:

  Customer Name : {0}
  Account Number: {1}

You can click on the link below to create a new Red Hat Login for this account
and obtain access to your subscriptions:

{2}

If you are not the technical manager who will utilize the Red Hat subscription
services purchased, please forward this email to the appropriate user within
your organization.  If they do not already have a Red Hat Login, that user may
follow the link above to establish a new one.

If you already have a login and it is linked to the above account, then no
action is required.  You can find the account number linked to an existing Red
Hat Login by logging into the following page:

http://www.redhat.com/support/

If you already have a Red Hat Login that is linked to a different account than
the one listed on this email, and would like to use that account to manage these
subscriptions, Red Hat can transfer them to your desired account.  Please
contact your regional Red Hat Customer Service Representative, using the contact
information provided at the following link:

{3}

Note to the Account Administrator (Organization Administrator): Before a new
user can access subscriptions, you must grant them the ability to see and manage
the subscriptions on your account.  This requires that a User Administration
entitlement exist on your account.  If required, please follow the link above
and contact your regional Red Hat Customer Service Representative to request
this feature.

Thank you for choosing Red Hat.

Sincerely,
Red Hat Account Management Team</source>
				<target>
Egregio cliente di Red Hat,

Il suo nome è presente all'interno di una ordinazione di nuove sottoscrizioni di Red Hat.
 Le suddette sottoscrizioni sono ora disponibili all'interno del seguente account:

  Nome Cliente: {0}
  Numero Account: {1}

Potete selezionare il link di seguito riportato e creare un nuovo login di Red Hat per l'account,
in modo da accedere alle vostre sottoscrizioni:

{2}

Se non siete il responsabile tecnico designato che dovrà utilizzare i servizi di sottoscrizione di Red Hat, allora inoltrate questa email all'utente appropriato all'interno della
vostra organizzazione.  Se il suddetto utente non possiede già un login di Red Hat, egli potrà
seguire il link in modo da stabilirne uno nuovo.

Se siete già in possesso di un login e se lo stesso è collegato all'account sopra riportato,
allora non sarà necessario eseguire alcuna azione.  È possibile trovare il numero dell'account collegato ad un login di Red
Hat già esistente, semplicemente registrandosi all'interno della seguente pagina:

http://www.redhat.com/support/

Se siete già in possesso di un Red Hat Login già collegato ad un account diversoda quello
presente in questa email, e desiderate utilizzare il suddetto account per gestire queste
sottoscrizioni, Red Hat è in grado di trasferirle nel vostro accout desiderato.  Vi preghiamo
di contattare il rappresentante del Red Hat Customer Service della vostra area, usando le informazioni
fornite nel seguente link:

{3}

Nota per l'Amministratore dell'Account (Organization Administrator): Prima che un nuovo
utente sia in grado di accedere alle sottoscrizioni in questione, sarà necessario da parte vostra garantire all'utente stesso la possibilità
di visualizzare e gestire le sottoscrizioni sul vostro account.  Ciò necessita della presenza di un entitlement di Gestione utente 'User Administration'
all'interno del vostro account.  Se necessario, vi preghiamo di seguire il link sopra riportato
e di contattare un rappresentante del Customer service di Red Hat della vostra zona, per richiedere
questo tipo di servizio.

Grazie per aver scelto Red Hat.

Cordialmente,
Il Red Hat Account Management Team</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.unchanneledsystem.subject">
				<source>Your Red Hat system is not able to receive service</source>
				<target>Il sistema Red Hat non è in grado di ricevere i servizi</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.unchanneledsystem.body">
				<source>
Dear Red Hat Customer,

The following system has been associated with your Red Hat login and
account in the past day, but could not be entitled to @@PRODUCT_NAME@@
services.

{0}

There are several reasons why this may have occurred:

1) You recently reinstalled a system and are attempting to associate
   the system with an existing, active subscription. Please ensure you
   delete your existing system profile on @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.

2) The number of systems you have connected to @@PRODUCT_NAME@@ exceeds
   the number of active Red Hat subscriptions associated with your
   account.  This may be because your subscriptions have expired or
   you need to purchase a Red Hat subscription.

   To check the expiration dates of your existing Red Hat
   subscriptions, please visit:

   https://www.redhat.com/apps/support/

   Log in and click on View and manage your subscriptions link.

3) You recently installed a Red Hat product and your subscription
   number was not successfully activated. If you would like to try and
   activate your subscription again, please visit:

   https://www.redhat.com/activate

For additional questions, please contact a Red Hat Customer Service
representative at:

http://www.redhat.com/about/contact/directory.html#custservice

Thank you for using @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.</source>
				<target>
Gentile cliente di Red Hat,

Il seguente sistema è stato associato al login e all'account di Red Hat,
ma purtroppo non risulta aver diritto ai servizi di
@@PRODUCT_NAME@@.

{0}

Questo problema si è verificato per diverse ragioni:

1) Recentemente è stato reinstallato un sistema e si è cercato di associarlo
   con una sottoscrizione esistente ed attiva. Si prega di cancellare
   il profilo del sistema esistente su @@PRODUCT_NAME@@

2) Il numero di sistemi collegati al @@PRODUCT_NAME@@ eccede il numero di
   sottoscrizioni Red Hat attive associate con l'account.
   Ciò può essere causato se le sottoscrizioni sono scadute,
   oppure se bisogna acquistare una sottoscrizione di Red Hat.

   Per controllare le date di scadenza delle sottoscrizioni di Red Hat
   esistenti, visitare:

   https://www.redhat.com/apps/support/

Eseguire il login e successivamente selezionare il link Visualizza e gestisci le
 sottoscrizioni
3) È stato recentemente installato un prodotto di Red Hat ed il numero di
   sottoscrizione non è stato attivato. Se si desidera attivare nuovamente la
   vostra sottoscrizione, visitare:

   https://www.redhat.com/activate

Per ulteriori chiarimenti, contattare un rappresentante del
Red Hat Customer Service su:

http://www.redhat.com/about/contact/directory.html#custservice

Grazie per aver scelto @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.errata.notification.body.summary">
				<source>
@@PRODUCT_NAME@@ has determined that the following advisory is applicable to
one or more of the systems you have registered:

Complete information about this errata can be found at the following location:
     {0}

{1} - {2}
------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Summary:
{3}

{4}{5}{6}
{7}
------------------------------------------------------------------------------</source>
				<target>
@@PRODUCT_NAME@@ ha determinato che il seguente advisory è applicabile ad uno
o più sistemi registrati:

Informazioni complete riguardanti questa errata sono di seguito disponibili:
     {0}

{1} - {2}
------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Sommario:
{3}

{4}{5}{6}
{7}
------------------------------------------------------------------------------</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.errata.notification.body.affectedheader">
				<source>
---------------------
Affected Systems List
---------------------
This Errata Advisory may apply to the systems listed below. If you know that
this errata does not apply to a system listed, it might be possible that the
package profile for that server is out of date. In that case you should run
'up2date -p' (RHEL 4 and below) or 'rhn-profile-sync' (RHEL 5 and above) as root on the system in question to refresh your software profile.</source>
				<target>
---------------------
Elenco dei sistemi interessati
---------------------
Questa Errata Advisory potrebbe interessare i sistemi di seguito riportati. Se ritenete che
l'errata non interessa un sistema in particolare, potrebbe significare che il profilo
del pacchetto per il server in questione non è aggiornato. In tal caso è consigliabile
 eseguire 'up2date -p' (RHEL 4 e versioni precedenti) o 'rhn-profile-sync' (RHEL 5 e versioni più recenti)come utente root sul sistema in questione, in modo da aggiornare il vostro profilo software.</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.errata.notification.body.onesystem">
				<source>
There is 1 affected system registered in 'Overview' (only systems for
which you have explicitly enabled Errata Alerts are shown).</source>
				<target>
È presente 1 sistema interessato e registrato su 'Panoramica' (vengono mostrati solo i
sistemi ai quali avete già abilitato gli Errata Alerts).</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.errata.notification.body.numsystems">
				<source>
There are {0} affected systems registered in 'Overview' (only systems for
which you have explicitly enabled Errata Alerts are shown).</source>
				<target>
Sono presenti {0} sistemi interessati registrati su 'Panoramica' (vengono mostrati solo i
sistemi ai quali avete già abilitato gli Errata Alerts).</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.errata.notification.body.affected">
				<source>
Release    Arch       Profile Name
---------- ---------- ---------------------------------------------
{0}

You may address the issues outlined in this advisory in two ways:

     - select your server name by clicking on its name from the list
       available at the following location, and then schedule an
       errata update for it:
           {1}

     - run the Update Agent on each affected server.</source>
				<target>
Release      Arch                    Nome profilo
----------------------------------------------------------------------------
{0}

È possibile risolrvere i problemi presenti su questa advisory in due modi:

     - selezionate il nome del vostro server cliccando sul nome presente all'interno dell'elenco
       disponibile nella seguente posizione, e successivamente programmate
       un errata update:
           {1}

     - eseguite Update Agent su ogni server interessato.</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.errata.notification.body.preferences">
				<source>
Changing Notification Preferences
---------------------------------
To enable/disable your Errata Alert preferences globally please log in to @@PRODUCT_NAME@@
and navigate from "Overview" / "Your Account" to the "Preferences" tab.

        URL: {0}

You can also enable/disable notification on a per system basis by selecting an
individual system from the "Systems List". From the individual system view
click the "Details" tab.

{1}
{2}</source>
				<target>
Modifica delle preferenze di notifica
---------------------------------
Per abilitare/disabilitare le preferenze del vostro Errata Alert è necessario eseguire il login su @@PRODUCT_NAME@@
e navigare attraverso "Panoramica" / "Il vostro Account" fino alla tabella "Preferenze".

        URL: {0}

È possibile altresì abilitare/disabilitare la notifica in base al sistema, semplicemente selezionando
un sistema individuale dalla tabella "Elenco sistemi". Dalla panoramica dei sistemi individuali
fate clic sulla tabella "Dettagli".

{1}
{2}</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="dailysummary.email.subject">
				<source>@@PRODUCT_NAME@@ Daily Status Report for {0}</source>
				<target>Rapporto giornaliero sullo Stato di @@PRODUCT_NAME@@ per {0}</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="dailysummary.email.body">
				<source>This is the @@PRODUCT_NAME@@ Status Report for your account {0}, as of {1}.

This email will be sent when any of the following apply:

1.  The system fails to check in with @@PRODUCT_NAME@@ within a 24-hour window.
2.  The system registers scheduled action activity.

{2}
{3}
Disabling this email:
----------------------

To learn how to disable this email for systems:

https://{4}/rhn/help/reference/en-US/s1-sm-your-rhn.jsp


Thank you for using @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.
{5}
{6}</source>
				<target>Questo è il rapporto sullo stato di @@PRODUCT_NAME@@ per il vostro account {0}, a partire da {1}.

Questa email verrà inviata ogni qualvolta si verificano i seguenti casi per i sistemi indicati:

1. Il sistema non è in grado di eseguire il checkin con @@PRODUCT_NAME@@ in un periodo di 24 ore.
2.  Il sistema registra attività programmate.

{2}
{3}
Disabilitare questa email:
----------------------

Per sapere come disabilitare questa email per un sistema:

https://{4}/rhn/help/reference/en-US/s1-sm-your-rhn.jsp


Grazie per aver utilizzato @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.
{5}
{6}</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.verification.notice.body">
				<source>
Dear @@PRODUCT_NAME@@ User,

This email is sent to validate the email address that you have
provided for your Red Hat login. Your Red Hat login, in combination
with an active Red Hat subscription, provides you with access to
systems management capabilities through @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.

To ensure the security of the account information associated with your
Red Hat login, please take a moment to click through the link below
and verify that we have the correct email address. If you do not
confirm your email address, your Red Hat login will eventually be
deactivated.

To confirm your email address, please visit the following URL:

{0}

Thank you for using @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.
{1}
{2}</source>
				<target>
Egregio utente di @@PRODUCT_NAME@@,

Questa email è stata inviata per convalidare l'indirizzo email inviato
per il suo login di Red Hat.
Il suddetto login, in combinazione con una sottoscrizione attiva di Red Hat,
fornisce un accesso alle capacità di gestione dei sistemi attraverso il @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.

Per garantire la sicurezza delle informazioni relative all'account associate con il suo login
di Red Hat, Le suggeriamo di spendere qualche secondo per navigare attraverso il
link di seguito riportato, e di verificare la correttezza dell'indirizzo email. Non
confermando il suo indirizzo email,  il login di Red Hat potrebbe essere
disabilitato.

Per confermare il suddetto indirizzo, consultare il seguente URL:

{0}

Grazie per aver usato @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.
{1}
{2}</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.verification.notice.subject">
				<source>Red Hat login Email Verification</source>
				<target>Verifica email di login di Red Hat</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.verification.warning.body">
				<source>
Dear @@PRODUCT_NAME@@ User,

This email is sent to validate the email address that you have
provided for your Red Hat login. Your Red Hat login, in combination
with an active Red Hat subscription, provides you with access to
systems management capabilities through @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.

To ensure the security of the account information associated with your
Red Hat login, please take a moment to click through the link below
and verify that we have the correct email address. If you do not
confirm your email address, your Red Hat login will eventually be
deactivated.

Please note that this is a final notice.  If you do not click through
this URL within the next 2 days, your Red Hat login will deactivated.

To confirm your email address, please visit the following URL:

{0}

Thank you for using @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.
{1}
{2}</source>
				<target>
Egregio utente di @@PRODUCT_NAME@@,

Questa email è stata inviata per convalidare l'indirizzo email
fornito per il suo Red Hat login. Il suddetto login, in combinazione
con una sottoscrizione attiva di Red Hat, fornisce un accesso alle
capacità di gestione dei sistemi attraverso il @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.

Per garantire la sicurezza delle informazioni relative all'account associate con il suo login
di Red Hat, Le suggeriamo di spendere qualche secondo per navigare
attraverso il link di seguito riportato, e di verificare la correttezza dell'indirizzo email.
Non confermando il suo indirizzo email, il login di Red Hat potrebbe essere
disabilitato.

Vi preghiamo di notare che questo risulta essere un avviso finale.  Se non confermate
il vostro indirizzo nei prossimi 2 giorni, il vostro login di Red Hat verrà disabilitato.

Per confermare il suddetto indirizzo, consultare il seguente URL:

{0}

Grazie per aver usato @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.
{1}
{2}</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.verification.warning.subject">
				<source>Red Hat Login Email Verification, Final Notice</source>
				<target>Verifica email login di Red Hat, avviso finale</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.satellitecert.graceperiod.subject">
				<source>Red Hat @@PRODUCT_NAME@@ Server Certificate expiration warning</source>
				<target>Avviso di scadenza del Certificato di @@PRODUCT_NAME@@ Server</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.satellitecert.graceperiod.body">
				<source>
Dear @@PRODUCT_NAME@@ User,

This email is being sent to you to inform you that your @@PRODUCT_NAME@@ Certificate
has expired on your local satellite {0}. After {1} day(s) the systems
management services provided by your @@PRODUCT_NAME@@ Server will become inaccessible.
Please contact your regional Red Hat Customer  Service Representative for information
on how to renew your @@PRODUCT_NAME@@ Certificate.

Thank you for using @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.
--the @@PRODUCT_NAME@@ Team</source>
				<target>
Egregio utente di @@PRODUCT_NAME@@,

Questa email le è stata recapitata per informarLa che il suo Certificato @@PRODUCT_NAME@@
sul suo satellite locale  {0} è scaduto. Fra {1} giorno(i) i servizi di gestione del sistema
forniti dal suo @@PRODUCT_NAME@@ Server non saranno più accessibili.
La preghiamo di contattare il suo rappresentante di zona del Red Hat Customer Service per informazioni
su come rinnovare il suo Certificato @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.

Grazie per aver scelto @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.
--il @@PRODUCT_NAME@@ Team</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.satellitecert.expired.subject">
				<source>Red Hat satellite certificate expiration notice</source>
				<target>Avviso di scadenza del certificato Red Hat satellite</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.satellitecert.expired.body">
				<source>
Dear @@PRODUCT_NAME@@ User,

This email is being sent to you to inform you that your @@PRODUCT_NAME@@ Certificate
has expired on your local satellite {0}. The system management services will be inaccessible
until your certificate is renewed. Please contact your regional Red Hat
Customer Service Representative for information on how to renew your @@PRODUCT_NAME@@ Certificate.


Thank you for using @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.
--the @@PRODUCT_NAME@@ Team</source>
				<target>
Egregio utente di Red Hat Network,

Questa email le è stata recapitata per informarLa che il suo Certificato @@PRODUCT_NAME@@
sul suo satellite locale {0} è scaduto. I servizi di gestione del sistema non saranno più accessibili
fino a quando il suo certificato non verrà rinnovato. La preghiamo di contattare il suo
rappresentante di zona del Red Hat Customer Service, per informazioni su come rinnovare il suo Certificato @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.


Grazie per aver scelto @PRODUCT_NAME@@.
--il @@PRODUCT_NAME@@ Team</target>
			</trans-unit>
		</body>
	</file>
</xliff>
