<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<xliff version="1.1" xmlns="urn:oasis:names:tc:xliff:document:1.1">
	<file source-language="en-US" target-language="fr-FR" datatype="po" original="en-US/template.xliff">
		<body>
			<trans-unit id="email.verify.subject">
				<source>@@PRODUCT_NAME@@ login Email Verification</source>
				<target>Vérification par courrier électronique de l'identifiant @@PRODUCT_NAME@@</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.verify.body">
				<source>Dear @@PRODUCT_NAME@@ User,

This email is sent to validate the email address that you have
provided for your Red Hat login. Your Red Hat login, in combination
with an active Red Hat subscription, provides you with access to
systems management capabilities through @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.

To ensure the security of the account information associated with your
Red Hat login, please take a moment to click the link below
and verify that we have the correct email address. If you do not
confirm your email address, your Red Hat login will eventually be
deactivated.

To confirm your email address, please visit the following URL:

{0}

Thank you for using @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.
{1}

{2}</source>
				<target>Cher utilisateur de @@PRODUCT_NAME@@,

Ce courrier électronique vous est envoyé pour valider l'adresse électronique
que vous avez saisie pour votre login Red Hat. Votre login Red Hat, avec un
abonnement Red Hat actif, vous permet d'accéder à des capacités de gestion
de systèmes via @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.

Pour assurer la sécurité des informations de compte associés à votre login
Red Hat, prenez le temps de cliquer sur le lien ci-dessous et de vérifier que
vous avez la bonne adresse électronique. Si vous ne confirmez pas votre
adresse électronique, votre login Red Hat sera éventuellement désactivé.

Pour la confirmer, rendez-vous à l'URL suivant :

{0}

Nous vous remercions d'utiliser @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.
{1}

{2}</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.newaccount.subject">
				<source>Your @@PRODUCT_NAME@@ Account is ready</source>
				<target>Votre compte @@PRODUCT_NAME@@ est prêt</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.newaccountbycreator.body">
				<source>Hello,

A Red Hat login has been created for you by {0} {1}. Your
Red Hat login, in combination with an active Red Hat subscription,
provides you with access to manage systems on @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.

  Red Hat login: {2}
       Password: {3}
         e-mail: {4}

  {5}

Important: Please change your password upon logging in.

Thank you for using @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.
{6}</source>
				<target>Bonjour,

Un login Red Hat a été créé pour vous par {0} {1}. Votre login
Red Hat, avec un abonnement Red Hat actif, vous permet d'accéder
à des capacités de gestion de systèmes sur @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.

  Login Red Hat : {2}
       Mot de passe : {3}
         adresse électronique : {4}

  {5}

Important : veuillez changer votre mot de passe à la connexion.

Nous vous remercions d'utiliser @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.
{6}</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.newaccount.body">
				<source>Hello,

A Red Hat login has been created for you. Your
Red Hat login, in combination with an active Red Hat subscription,
provides you with access to manage systems on @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.

  Red Hat login: {0}
       Password: {1}
         e-mail: {2}

  {3}

Important: Please change your password upon logging in.

Thank you for using @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.
{4}</source>
				<target>Bonjour,

Un login Red Hat a été créé pour vous. Votre login
Red Hat, avec un abonnement Red Hat actif, vous permet d'accéder
à des capacités de gestion de systèmes sur @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.

  Login Red Hat : {0}
       Mot de passe : {1}
         adresse électronique : {2}

  {3}

Important : veuillez changer votre mot de passe à la connexion.

Nous vous remercions d'utiliser @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.
{4}</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.newaccount.pam.body">
				<source>Hello,

A Red Hat login has been created for you by {0} {1}.  Your
Red Hat login, in combination with an active Red Hat subscription,
provides you with access to manage systems on @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.

  Red Hat login: {2}
         e-mail: {4}

  {5}

Thank you for using @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.
{6}</source>
				<target>Bonjour,

Un login Red Hat a été créé pour vous par {0} {1}. Votre login
Red Hat, avec un abonnement Red Hat actif, vous permet d'accéder
à des capacités de gestion de systèmes sur @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.

  Login Red Hat : {2}
         adresse électronique : {4}

  {5}

Nous vous remercions d'utiliser @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.
{6}</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.newuser.subject">
				<source>@@PRODUCT_NAME@@ User Created: {0} ({1}, {2} &lt;{3}&gt;)</source>
				<target>Utilisateur @@PRODUCT_NAME@@ créé : {0} ({1}, {2} &lt;{3}&gt;)</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.newuser.body">
				<source>Hello,

A new user has been added to your account.

{0}

To see all the active users and Red Hat logins associated with your account,
please visit:

  {1}

Thank you for using @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.
{2}</source>
				<target>Bonjour,

Un nouvel utilisateur a été ajouté à votre compte.

{0}

Pour afficher tous utilisateurs actifs et les logins Red Hat associés
à votre compte, rendez-vous à l'adresse suivante :

  {1}

Nous vous remercions d'utiliser @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.
{2}</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.user.deleted.subject">
				<source>@@PRODUCT_NAME@@ Account Deactivated: {0}</source>
				<target>Compte @@PRODUCT_NAME@@ désactivé : {0}</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.user.deleted.body">
				<source>
The Red Hat login {0} has been deactivated in response to your request.

Thank you for contacting Red Hat.</source>
				<target>
Le login Red Hat {0} a été désactivé suivant votre demande.

Merci d'avoir contacté Red Hat.</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.newuser.bala.subject">
				<source>Red Hat login creation request</source>
				<target>Demande de création d'un login Red Hat</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.newuser.bala.footer">
				<source>
For additional information in German language, please visit our Website:
{0}</source>
				<target>
Pour davantage d'informations en allemand, rendez-vous sur notre site Web&amp;nbsp;:
{0}</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.newuser.bala.footer2">
				<source>
For French, click here: {0}</source>
				<target>
Pour le français, cliquez ici&amp;nbsp;: {0}</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.newuser.bala.body">
				<source>
Dear Red Hat Customer,

You were recently named on an order for new Red Hat subscriptions.  These
subscriptions are now available in the following account:

  Customer Name : {0}
  Account Number: {1}

You can click on the link below to create a new Red Hat Login for this account
and obtain access to your subscriptions:

{2}

If you are not the technical manager who will utilize the Red Hat subscription
services purchased, please forward this email to the appropriate user within
your organization.  If they do not already have a Red Hat Login, that user may
follow the link above to establish a new one.

If you already have a login and it is linked to the above account, then no
action is required.  You can find the account number linked to an existing Red
Hat Login by logging into the following page:

http://www.redhat.com/support/

If you already have a Red Hat Login that is linked to a different account than
the one listed on this email, and would like to use that account to manage these
subscriptions, Red Hat can transfer them to your desired account.  Please
contact your regional Red Hat Customer Service Representative, using the contact
information provided at the following link:

{3}

Note to the Account Administrator (Organization Administrator): Before a new
user can access subscriptions, you must grant them the ability to see and manage
the subscriptions on your account.  This requires that a User Administration
entitlement exist on your account.  If required, please follow the link above
and contact your regional Red Hat Customer Service Representative to request
this feature.

Thank you for choosing Red Hat.

Sincerely,
Red Hat Account Management Team</source>
				<target>
Cher client de Red Hat,

Vous avez été récemment nommé sur une demande de nouveaux abonnements Red Hat.
Ces abonnements sont désormais disponibles dans le compte suivant&amp;nbsp;:

  Nom de client&amp;nbsp;: {0}
  Numéro de compte&amp;nbsp;: {1}

Vous pouvez cliquer sur le lien ci-dessous pour créer un nouveau login
Red Hat pour ce compte et obtenir accès à vos abonnements&amp;nbsp;:

{2}

Si vous n'êtes pas le directeur technique qui utilisera les services d'abonnements
Red Hat achetés, transmettez ce message à l'utilisateur approprié de votre organisation.
Si il n'a pas encore de login Red Hat, cet utilisateur peut suivre le lien ci-dessus pour
en créer un.

Si vous avez déjà un login et si il est lié au compte ci-dessus, aucune action n'est alors
requise. Vous trouverez le numéro de compte lié à un login Red Hat existant en vous
connectant sur la page suivante&amp;nbsp;:

http://www.redhat.com/support/

Si vous avez déjà un login Red Hat lié à un compte différent du compte listé dans ce
courrier et que vous souhaitez utiliser ce compte pour gérer ces abonnements, Red Hat
peut les transférer sur votre compte désiré. Contactez le représentant du service
clientèle Red Hat de votre région, en utilisant les informations de contact fournies sur
le lien suivant&amp;nbsp;:

{3}

Note pour l'administrateur de comptes (administrateur d'organisation)&amp;nbsp;: avant
 qu'un nouvel utilisateur puisse accéder aux abonnements, vous devez leur donner
la possibilité de voir et de gérer les abonnements de votre compte. Un droit d'accès
de gestion d'utilisateurs doit donc exister sur votre compte. En cas de besoin, suivez le
lien ci-dessus et contactez le représentant du service clientèle Red Hat de votre région
pour demander cette fonction.

Merci d'avoir choisi Red Hat.

Cordialement,
L'équipe de gestion de comptes de Red Hat</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.unchanneledsystem.subject">
				<source>Your Red Hat system is not able to receive service</source>
				<target>Votre système Red Hat ne peut pas recevoir ce service</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.unchanneledsystem.body">
				<source>
Dear Red Hat Customer,

The following system has been associated with your Red Hat login and
account in the past day, but could not be entitled to @@PRODUCT_NAME@@
services.

{0}

There are several reasons why this may have occurred:

1) You recently reinstalled a system and are attempting to associate
   the system with an existing, active subscription. Please ensure you
   delete your existing system profile on @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.

2) The number of systems you have connected to @@PRODUCT_NAME@@ exceeds
   the number of active Red Hat subscriptions associated with your
   account.  This may be because your subscriptions have expired or
   you need to purchase a Red Hat subscription.

   To check the expiration dates of your existing Red Hat
   subscriptions, please visit:

   https://www.redhat.com/apps/support/

   Log in and click on View and manage your subscriptions link.

3) You recently installed a Red Hat product and your subscription
   number was not successfully activated. If you would like to try and
   activate your subscription again, please visit:

   https://www.redhat.com/activate

For additional questions, please contact a Red Hat Customer Service
representative at:

http://www.redhat.com/about/contact/directory.html#custservice

Thank you for using @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.</source>
				<target>
Cher client de Red Hat,

Le système suivant a été associé à votre identifiant et à votre compte
Red Hat mais n'a pas reçu de droits d'accès aux services @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.

{0}

Il y a plusieurs raisons pour lesquelles ceci aurait pu se produire :

1) Vous venez de réinstaller un système et essayez de l'associer à un
   abonnement actif existant. Veuillez vous assurer de bien supprimer
   votre profil système existant sur @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.

2) Le nombre de systèmes que vous avez connectés à @@PRODUCT_NAME@@
   dépasse le nombre d'abonnements Red Hat actifs associés à votre
   compte. Il se peut que ceci arrive parceque vos abonnements aient expirés ou parceque vous
   devez acheter un abonnement Red Hat.

   Pour vérifier les dates d'expiration de vos abonnements Red Hat
   existants, rendez-vous à l'adresse suivante :

   https://www.redhat.com/apps/support/

   Connectez-vous et cliquez sur le lien Afficher et gérer vos abonnements.

3) Vous venez d'installer un produit Red Hat et votre numéro d'abonnement
   n'a pas été activé. Si vous souhaitez essayer d'activer à nouveau votre
   abonnement, rendez-vous à l'adresse suivante :

   https://www.redhat.com/activate

Pour toute autre question, contactez un représentant du service clientèle de Red Hat à l'adresse suivante&amp;nbsp;:

http://www.redhat.com/about/contact/directory.html#custservice

Merci d'utiliser @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.errata.notification.body.summary">
				<source>
@@PRODUCT_NAME@@ has determined that the following advisory is applicable to
one or more of the systems you have registered:

Complete information about this errata can be found at the following location:
     {0}

{1} - {2}
------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Summary:
{3}

{4}{5}{6}
{7}
------------------------------------------------------------------------------</source>
				<target>
@@PRODUCT_NAME@@ a décidé que l'avertissement suivant était applicable à un
ou plusieurs des systèmes que vous avez enregistrés.

Vous pouvez trouver des informations complètes sur cet errata à l'emplacement suivant :

     {0}

{1} - {2}
------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Résumé :
{3}

{4}{5}{6}
{7}
------------------------------------------------------------------------------</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.errata.notification.body.affectedheader">
				<source>
---------------------
Affected Systems List
---------------------
This Errata Advisory may apply to the systems listed below. If you know that
this errata does not apply to a system listed, it might be possible that the
package profile for that server is out of date. In that case you should run
'up2date -p' (RHEL 4 and below) or 'rhn-profile-sync' (RHEL 5 and above) as root on the system in question to refresh your software profile.</source>
				<target>
---------------------
Affected Systems List
---------------------
This Errata Advisory may apply to the systems listed below. If you know that
this errata does not apply to a system listed, it might be possible that the
package profile for that server is out of date. In that case you should run
'up2date -p' (RHEL 4 and below) or 'rhn-profile-sync' (RHEL 5 and above) as root on the system in question to refresh your software profile.</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.errata.notification.body.onesystem">
				<source>
There is 1 affected system registered in 'Overview' (only systems for
which you have explicitly enabled Errata Alerts are shown).</source>
				<target>
1 système affecté est enregistré dans "Aperçu" (seulement les systèmes
pour lesquels vous avez activé les alertes d'errata sont affichés).</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.errata.notification.body.numsystems">
				<source>
There are {0} affected systems registered in 'Overview' (only systems for
which you have explicitly enabled Errata Alerts are shown).</source>
				<target>
{0} systèmes affectés sont enregistrés dans "Aperçu" (seulement les systèmes
pour lesquels vous avez activé les alertes d'errata sont affichés).</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.errata.notification.body.affected">
				<source>
Release    Arch       Profile Name
---------- ---------- ---------------------------------------------
{0}

You may address the issues outlined in this advisory in two ways:

     - select your server name by clicking on its name from the list
       available at the following location, and then schedule an
       errata update for it:
           {1}

     - run the Update Agent on each affected server.</source>
				<target>
Sortie    Arche       Nom de profil
---------- ---------- ---------------------------------------------
{0}

Vous pouvez adresser les problèmes soulignés dans cet avertissement de deux manières :

     - sélectionnez votre nom de serveur en cliquant sur son nom à partir de la liste
       disponible à l'emplacement suivant, puis programmez une mise à jour
       d'errata pour ce serveur :
           {1}

     - démarrer l'agent de mise à jour sur chaque serveur affecté.</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.errata.notification.body.preferences">
				<source>
Changing Notification Preferences
---------------------------------
To enable/disable your Errata Alert preferences globally please log in to @@PRODUCT_NAME@@
and navigate from "Overview" / "Your Account" to the "Preferences" tab.

        URL: {0}

You can also enable/disable notification on a per system basis by selecting an
individual system from the "Systems List". From the individual system view
click the "Details" tab.

{1}
{2}</source>
				<target>
Changer les préférences de notification
---------------------------------
Pour activer/désactiver vos préférences d'alerte d'errata globalement, connectez-vous à @@PRODUCT_NAME@@
et allez à partir de "Aperçu"/"Votre compte" sur l'onglet "Préférences".

        Lien : {0}

Vous pouvez également activer/désactiver les notifications pour chaque système en sélectionnant un
système individuel à partir de la "Liste des systèmes". À partir de l'affichage individuel d'un système,
cliquez sur l'onglet "Détails".

{1}
{2}</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="dailysummary.email.subject">
				<source>@@PRODUCT_NAME@@ Daily Status Report for {0}</source>
				<target>Rapport de statut quotidien de @@PRODUCT_NAME@@ pour {0}</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="dailysummary.email.body">
				<source>This is the @@PRODUCT_NAME@@ Status Report for your account {0}, as of {1}.

This email will be sent when any of the following apply:

1.  The system fails to check in with @@PRODUCT_NAME@@ within a 24-hour window.
2.  The system registers scheduled action activity.

{2}
{3}
Disabling this email:
----------------------

To learn how to disable this email for systems:

https://{4}/rhn/help/reference/en-US/s1-sm-your-rhn.jsp


Thank you for using @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.
{5}
{6}</source>
				<target>Voici le rapport de statut de @@PRODUCT_NAME@@ pour votre compte {0}, pour le {1}.

Ce message sera envoyé lorsque l'une des conditions suivantes s'applique
aux systèmes spécifiés :

1.  Le système ne s'est pas connecté à @@PRODUCT_NAME@@ dans les dernières 24 heures.
2.  Le système enregistre des actions programmées actives.

{2}
{3}
Désactiver ce message :
----------------------

Pour apprendre comment désactiver ce message pour les systèmes :

https://{4}/rhn/help/reference/en/s1-sm-your-rhn.jsp


Nous vous remercions d'utiliser @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.
{5}
{6}</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.verification.notice.body">
				<source>
Dear @@PRODUCT_NAME@@ User,

This email is sent to validate the email address that you have
provided for your Red Hat login. Your Red Hat login, in combination
with an active Red Hat subscription, provides you with access to
systems management capabilities through @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.

To ensure the security of the account information associated with your
Red Hat login, please take a moment to click through the link below
and verify that we have the correct email address. If you do not
confirm your email address, your Red Hat login will eventually be
deactivated.

To confirm your email address, please visit the following URL:

{0}

Thank you for using @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.
{1}
{2}</source>
				<target>
Cher utilisateur de @@PRODUCT_NAME@@,

Ce courrier électronique vous est envoyé pour valider l'adresse électronique
que vous avez saisie pour votre login Red Hat. Votre login Red Hat, avec un
abonnement Red Hat actif, vous permet d'accéder à des capacités de gestion
de systèmes via @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.

Pour assurer la sécurité des informations de compte associés à votre login
Red Hat, prenez le temps de cliquer sur le lien ci-dessous et de vérifier que
vous avez la bonne adresse électronique. Si vous ne confirmez pas votre
adresse électronique, votre login Red Hat sera éventuellement désactivé.

Pour la confirmer, rendez-vous à l'URL suivant :

{0}

Nous vous remercions d'utiliser @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.
{1}
{2}</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.verification.notice.subject">
				<source>Red Hat login Email Verification</source>
				<target>Vérification par courrier électronique du login Red Hat</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.verification.warning.body">
				<source>
Dear @@PRODUCT_NAME@@ User,

This email is sent to validate the email address that you have
provided for your Red Hat login. Your Red Hat login, in combination
with an active Red Hat subscription, provides you with access to
systems management capabilities through @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.

To ensure the security of the account information associated with your
Red Hat login, please take a moment to click through the link below
and verify that we have the correct email address. If you do not
confirm your email address, your Red Hat login will eventually be
deactivated.

Please note that this is a final notice.  If you do not click through
this URL within the next 2 days, your Red Hat login will deactivated.

To confirm your email address, please visit the following URL:

{0}

Thank you for using @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.
{1}
{2}</source>
				<target>
Cher utilisateur de @@PRODUCT_NAME@@,

Ce courrier électronique vous est envoyé pour valider l'adresse électronique
que vous avez saisie pour votre login Red Hat. Votre login Red Hat, avec un
abonnement Red Hat actif, vous permet d'accéder à des capacités de gestion
de systèmes via Red Hat Network.

Pour assurer la sécurité des informations de compte associés à votre login
Red Hat, prenez le temps de cliquer sur le lien ci-dessous et de vérifier que
vous avez la bonne adresse électronique. Si vous ne confirmez pas votre
adresse électronique, votre login Red Hat sera éventuellement désactivé.

Notez que cet avertissement est le dernier. Si vous ne visitez pas cet
URL dans les 2 prochains jours, votre login Red Hat sera désactivé.

Pour confirmer votre adresse électronique, rendez-vous à l'URL suivant :

{0}

Nous vous remercions d'utiliser @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.
{1}
{2}</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.verification.warning.subject">
				<source>Red Hat Login Email Verification, Final Notice</source>
				<target>Vérification par courrier électronique du login Red Hat, dernier avis</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.satellitecert.graceperiod.subject">
				<source>Red Hat @@PRODUCT_NAME@@ Server Certificate expiration warning</source>
				<target>Avertissement d'expiration du certificat du serveur @@PRODUCT_NAME@@ de Red Hat</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.satellitecert.graceperiod.body">
				<source>
Dear @@PRODUCT_NAME@@ User,

This email is being sent to you to inform you that your @@PRODUCT_NAME@@ Certificate
has expired on your local satellite {0}. After {1} day(s) the systems
management services provided by your @@PRODUCT_NAME@@ Server will become inaccessible.
Please contact your regional Red Hat Customer  Service Representative for information
on how to renew your @@PRODUCT_NAME@@ Certificate.

Thank you for using @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.
--the @@PRODUCT_NAME@@ Team</source>
				<target>
Cher utilisateur de Red Hat Network,

Ce courrier électronique vous est envoyé pour vous informer que le certificat de votre @@PRODUCT_NAME@@
a expiré sur votre Satellite local {0}. Dans {1} jour(s) les services de gestion
des systèmes fournient par votre serveur @@PRODUCT_NAME@@ deviendront inaccessibles.
Contactez le représentant du service clientèle Red Hat de votre région pour davantage d'informations
concernant le renouvellement de votre certificat @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.

Nous vous remercions d'utiliser @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.
-- l'équipe @@PRODUCT_NAME@@</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.satellitecert.expired.subject">
				<source>Red Hat satellite certificate expiration notice</source>
				<target>Avis d'expiration du certificat du Satellite Red Hat</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.satellitecert.expired.body">
				<source>
Dear @@PRODUCT_NAME@@ User,

This email is being sent to you to inform you that your @@PRODUCT_NAME@@ Certificate
has expired on your local satellite {0}. The system management services will be inaccessible
until your certificate is renewed. Please contact your regional Red Hat
Customer Service Representative for information on how to renew your @@PRODUCT_NAME@@ Certificate.


Thank you for using @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.
--the @@PRODUCT_NAME@@ Team</source>
				<target>
Cher utilisateur de @@PRODUCT_NAME@@,

Ce courrier électronique vous est envoyé pour vous informer que le certificat de votre @@PRODUCT_NAME@@
a expiré sur votre Satellite local {0}. Les services de gestion du système seront inaccessibles
jusqu'à ce que votre certificat soit renouvelé. Contactez le représentant du service clientèle
Red Hat de votre région pour davantage d'informations concernant le renouvellement de votre certificat @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.


Nous vous remercions d'utiliser @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.
-- l'équipe @@PRODUCT_NAME@@</target>
			</trans-unit>
		</body>
	</file>
</xliff>
