<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<xliff version="1.1" xmlns="urn:oasis:names:tc:xliff:document:1.1">
	<file source-language="en-US" target-language="es-ES" datatype="po" original="en-US/template.xliff">
		<body>
			<trans-unit id="email.verify.subject">
				<source>@@PRODUCT_NAME@@ login Email Verification</source>
				<target>Verificación de correo-e de nombre de usuario de @@PRODUCT_NAME@@</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.verify.body">
				<source>Dear @@PRODUCT_NAME@@ User,

This email is sent to validate the email address that you have
provided for your Red Hat login. Your Red Hat login, in combination
with an active Red Hat subscription, provides you with access to
systems management capabilities through @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.

To ensure the security of the account information associated with your
Red Hat login, please take a moment to click the link below
and verify that we have the correct email address. If you do not
confirm your email address, your Red Hat login will eventually be
deactivated.

To confirm your email address, please visit the following URL:

{0}

Thank you for using @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.
{1}

{2}</source>
				<target>Estimado usuario de @@PRODUCT_NAME@@,

Este correo-e es enviado con el fin de validar la dirección de correo-e
que usted ha proporcionado para obtener un nombre de usuario en Red Hat.
Su nombre de usuario de Red Hat, junto con una suscripción activa de Red Hat,
le brinda acceso a las funciones de administración de sistemas
a través de @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.

Para garantizar la seguridad de la información de la cuenta asociada
con su nombre de usuario de Red Hat, por favor haga clic en el enlace proporcionado
a continuación, y verifique que la información de correo-e sea la correcta.
Si no confirma su dirección de correo-e, su nombre de usuario de Red Hat será
al final desactivado.

Para confirmar su dirección de correo-e, por favor visite la siguiente la URL:

{0}

Gracias por usar @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.
{1}

{2} </target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.newaccount.subject">
				<source>Your @@PRODUCT_NAME@@ Account is ready</source>
				<target>Su cuenta de @@PRODUCT_NAME@@ está lista</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.newaccountbycreator.body">
				<source>Hello,

A Red Hat login has been created for you by {0} {1}. Your
Red Hat login, in combination with an active Red Hat subscription,
provides you with access to manage systems on @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.

  Red Hat login: {2}
       Password: {3}
         e-mail: {4}

  {5}

Important: Please change your password upon logging in.

Thank you for using @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.
{6}</source>
				<target>Hola,

Un nombre de usuario de Red Hat ha sido creado para usted por {0} {1}. Su nombre de usuario de Red Hat
, junto con una suscripción activa de Red Hat, le brindan acceso a
 las funciones de administración de sistemas de @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.

Nombre de usuario de Red Hat: {2}
Contraseña: {3}
Correo-e: {4}

{5}

Importante: por favor cambie su contraseña una vez entre a RHN.

Gracias por usar @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.
{6}</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.newaccount.body">
				<source>Hello,

A Red Hat login has been created for you. Your
Red Hat login, in combination with an active Red Hat subscription,
provides you with access to manage systems on @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.

  Red Hat login: {0}
       Password: {1}
         e-mail: {2}

  {3}

Important: Please change your password upon logging in.

Thank you for using @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.
{4}</source>
				<target>Hola,

Un nombre de usuario de Red Hat ha sido creado para usted. Su nombre de usuario de Red Hat
, junto con una suscripción activa de Red Hat, le brindan acceso a
 las funciones de administración de sistemas de @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.

Nombre de usuario de Red Hat: {0}
Contraseña: {1}
Correo-e: {2}

{3}

Importante: por favor cambie su contraseña una vez entre a RHN.

Gracias por usar @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.
{4}</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.newaccount.pam.body">
				<source>Hello,

A Red Hat login has been created for you by {0} {1}.  Your
Red Hat login, in combination with an active Red Hat subscription,
provides you with access to manage systems on @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.

  Red Hat login: {2}
         e-mail: {4}

  {5}

Thank you for using @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.
{6}</source>
				<target>Hola,

Un nombre de usuario de Red Hat ha sido creado para usted por {0} {1}. Su nombre de usuario de Red Hat
, junto con una suscripción activa de Red Hat, le brindan acceso a
 las funciones de administración de sistemas de @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.

Nombre de usuario de Red Hat: {2}
Correo-e: {4}

{5}

Gracias por usar @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.
{6}</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.newuser.subject">
				<source>@@PRODUCT_NAME@@ User Created: {0} ({1}, {2} &lt;{3}&gt;)</source>
				<target>Usuario @@PRODUCT_NAME@@ creado: {0} ({1}, {2} &lt;{3}&gt;)</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.newuser.body">
				<source>Hello,

A new user has been added to your account.

{0}

To see all the active users and Red Hat logins associated with your account,
please visit:

  {1}

Thank you for using @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.
{2}</source>
				<target>Hola,

Un nuevo usuario ha sido añadido a su cuenta.

{0}

Para ver todos los usuario activos y los nombre de usuarios de Red Hat asociados con sus cuentas,
por favor visite:

{1}

Gracias por usar @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.
{2}</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.user.deleted.subject">
				<source>@@PRODUCT_NAME@@ Account Deactivated: {0}</source>
				<target>Cuenta @@PRODUCT_NAME@@ desactivada: {0}</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.user.deleted.body">
				<source>
The Red Hat login {0} has been deactivated in response to your request.

Thank you for contacting Red Hat.</source>
				<target>
El nombre de usuario de Red Hat {0} ha sido desactivado en respuesta a su solicitud.

Gracias por contactar Red Hat.</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.newuser.bala.subject">
				<source>Red Hat login creation request</source>
				<target>Solicitud de creación de un nombre de usuario de Red Hat</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.newuser.bala.footer">
				<source>
For additional information in German language, please visit our Website:
{0}</source>
				<target>
Para mayor información en alemán, por favor visite nuestro sitio web:
{0}</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.newuser.bala.footer2">
				<source>
For French, click here: {0}</source>
				<target>
En francés, haga clic aquí: {0}</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.newuser.bala.body">
				<source>
Dear Red Hat Customer,

You were recently named on an order for new Red Hat subscriptions.  These
subscriptions are now available in the following account:

  Customer Name : {0}
  Account Number: {1}

You can click on the link below to create a new Red Hat Login for this account
and obtain access to your subscriptions:

{2}

If you are not the technical manager who will utilize the Red Hat subscription
services purchased, please forward this email to the appropriate user within
your organization.  If they do not already have a Red Hat Login, that user may
follow the link above to establish a new one.

If you already have a login and it is linked to the above account, then no
action is required.  You can find the account number linked to an existing Red
Hat Login by logging into the following page:

http://www.redhat.com/support/

If you already have a Red Hat Login that is linked to a different account than
the one listed on this email, and would like to use that account to manage these
subscriptions, Red Hat can transfer them to your desired account.  Please
contact your regional Red Hat Customer Service Representative, using the contact
information provided at the following link:

{3}

Note to the Account Administrator (Organization Administrator): Before a new
user can access subscriptions, you must grant them the ability to see and manage
the subscriptions on your account.  This requires that a User Administration
entitlement exist on your account.  If required, please follow the link above
and contact your regional Red Hat Customer Service Representative to request
this feature.

Thank you for choosing Red Hat.

Sincerely,
Red Hat Account Management Team</source>
				<target>
Estimado usuario de Red Hat:

Usted ha sido recientemente nombrado en una orden de adquisición de suscripciones
de Red Hat. Estas suscripciones están disponibles en la siguiente cuenta:

  Nombre de usuario: {0}
  Número de cuenta: {1}

Haga clic en el enlace dado a continuación para crear un nuevo nombre de usuario de Red Hat
para esta cuenta y obtener acceso a sus suscripciones:

{2}

Si usted no es el administrador técnico que utilizará los servicios adquiridos con la
suscripción de Red Hat, por favor envíe este correo-e al usuario apropiado dentro de
su organización.  Si este usuario no tiene un nombre de usuario en Red Hat, puede crear un
nuevo nombre de usuario haciendo clic en el enlace superior.

Si ya tiene un nombre de usuario y está conectado a la cuenta arriba mencionada, no se
requerirá ninguna acción. Puede encontrar el número de cuenta de un nombre de usuario de Red
Hat existente en la siguiente página:

http://www.redhat.com/support/

Si ya tiene un nombre de usuario de Red Hat conectado a una cuenta diferente a la
listada en este correo-e y desea utilizar esa cuenta para administrar estas
suscripciones, Red Hat puede transferirlas a la cuenta deseada. Por favor
contacte a su representante de servicio al cliente Red Hat en su región utilizando
la información de contacto proporcionada en el siguiente enlace:

{3}

Nota al Administrador de la cuenta (Administrador de la organización): antes de
que un nuevo usuario pueda acceder a las suscripciones, usted debe otorgar los
permisos para ver y administrar las suscripciones en su cuenta. Esto requiere la existencia
de un derecho de Administración de Usuario en su cuenta. De ser necesario, por favor
siga el enlace dado y contacte a su Representante de servicio al cliente de Red Hat de su
región para solicitar esta funcionalidad.

Gracias por escoger Red Hat.

Atentamente,
Red Hat Account Management Team</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.unchanneledsystem.subject">
				<source>Your Red Hat system is not able to receive service</source>
				<target>Su sistema Red Hat no está en la capacidad de recibir servicios</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.unchanneledsystem.body">
				<source>
Dear Red Hat Customer,

The following system has been associated with your Red Hat login and
account in the past day, but could not be entitled to @@PRODUCT_NAME@@
services.

{0}

There are several reasons why this may have occurred:

1) You recently reinstalled a system and are attempting to associate
   the system with an existing, active subscription. Please ensure you
   delete your existing system profile on @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.

2) The number of systems you have connected to @@PRODUCT_NAME@@ exceeds
   the number of active Red Hat subscriptions associated with your
   account.  This may be because your subscriptions have expired or
   you need to purchase a Red Hat subscription.

   To check the expiration dates of your existing Red Hat
   subscriptions, please visit:

   https://www.redhat.com/apps/support/

   Log in and click on View and manage your subscriptions link.

3) You recently installed a Red Hat product and your subscription
   number was not successfully activated. If you would like to try and
   activate your subscription again, please visit:

   https://www.redhat.com/activate

For additional questions, please contact a Red Hat Customer Service
representative at:

http://www.redhat.com/about/contact/directory.html#custservice

Thank you for using @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.</source>
				<target>
Estimado cliente de Red Hat:

El siguiente sistema ha sido asociado con su nombre de usuario de Red Hat y
con su cuenta en los últimos días, pero no pudo recibir los derechos
a los servicios de @@PRODUCT_NAME@@

{0}

Hay varias razones que pudieron causar esta anomalía:

1) Usted ha reinstalado recientemente un sistema y está intentando asociar
   el sistema con una suscripción activa ya existente. Por favor asegúrese
   de borrar su perfil de sistema existente en @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.

2) El número de sistemas que usted ha conectado a @@PRODUCT_NAME@@ excede
   el número de suscripciones activas de Red Hat asociadas con su
   cuenta.  Esto puede ser debido a que su suscripción ha expirado
   o a que necesita adquirir una suscripción de Red Hat.

   Para revisar la fecha de vencimiento de sus suscripciones de Red Hat
existentes, por favor visite:

   https://www.redhat.com/apps/support/

   Inicie una sesión y haga clic en el enlace Ver y administrar sus suscripciones.

3) Usted instaló recientemente un producto de Red Hat y su número
   de suscripción no fue activado satisfactoriamente. Si desea reintentar
   activar su suscripción, por favor visite:

   https://www.redhat.com/activate

Si tiene preguntas adicionales, por favor contacte a un representante de servicio
al cliente de Red Hat en:

http://www.redhat.com/about/contact/directory.html#custservice

Gracias por utilizar @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.errata.notification.body.summary">
				<source>
@@PRODUCT_NAME@@ has determined that the following advisory is applicable to
one or more of the systems you have registered:

Complete information about this errata can be found at the following location:
     {0}

{1} - {2}
------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Summary:
{3}

{4}{5}{6}
{7}
------------------------------------------------------------------------------</source>
				<target>
@@PRODUCT_NAME@@ ha determinado que la siguiente recomendación es aplicable a
uno o más sistemas registrados:

Toda la información sobre esta errata puede encontrarse en:
     {0}

{1} - {2}
------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Resumen:
{3}

{4}{5}{6}
{7}
------------------------------------------------------------------------------</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.errata.notification.body.affectedheader">
				<source>
---------------------
Affected Systems List
---------------------
This Errata Advisory may apply to the systems listed below. If you know that
this errata does not apply to a system listed, it might be possible that the
package profile for that server is out of date. In that case you should run
'up2date -p' (RHEL 4 and below) or 'rhn-profile-sync' (RHEL 5 and above) as root on the system in question to refresh your software profile.</source>
				<target>
---------------------
Lista de sistemas afectados
---------------------
Esta recomendación de errata puede ser aplicada a los sistemas listados a continuación.
Si alguna de las erratas no es aplicable a alguno de los sistemas listados, es probable
que el perfil de paquetes de ese sistema esté desactualizado. En dicho caso, ejecute
'up2date -p' (en RHEL4 o anterior) o 'rhn-profile-sync' (en RHEL 5 y superior) como root sobre el sistema en cuestión para recrear el perfil de software.</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.errata.notification.body.onesystem">
				<source>
There is 1 affected system registered in 'Overview' (only systems for
which you have explicitly enabled Errata Alerts are shown).</source>
				<target>
Hay un sistema afectado registrado en 'Visión General' (solo se muestran los sistemas
en los cuales la alerta de erratas está activada).</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.errata.notification.body.numsystems">
				<source>
There are {0} affected systems registered in 'Overview' (only systems for
which you have explicitly enabled Errata Alerts are shown).</source>
				<target>
Hay {0} sistemas afectados registrados en 'Visión General' (solo se muestran los sistemas
en los cuales la alerta de erratas está activada).</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.errata.notification.body.affected">
				<source>
Release    Arch       Profile Name
---------- ---------- ---------------------------------------------
{0}

You may address the issues outlined in this advisory in two ways:

     - select your server name by clicking on its name from the list
       available at the following location, and then schedule an
       errata update for it:
           {1}

     - run the Update Agent on each affected server.</source>
				<target>
Lanzamiento    Arco       Nombre de Perfil
---------- ---------- ---------------------------------------------
{0}

Puede abordar el problema esbozado en la recomendación de dos maneras:

     - seleccione el nombre de servidor haciendo clic sobre el nombre en la lista
       disponible en la siguiente dirección y programe una actualización de
       errata para éste:
           {1}

     - ejecute el agente de actualización en cada servidor afectado.</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.errata.notification.body.preferences">
				<source>
Changing Notification Preferences
---------------------------------
To enable/disable your Errata Alert preferences globally please log in to @@PRODUCT_NAME@@
and navigate from "Overview" / "Your Account" to the "Preferences" tab.

        URL: {0}

You can also enable/disable notification on a per system basis by selecting an
individual system from the "Systems List". From the individual system view
click the "Details" tab.

{1}
{2}</source>
				<target>
Cambio de las preferencias de notificación
---------------------------------
Para activar/desactivar las preferencias de alerta de errata de una manera global,
inicie una sesión en @@PRODUCT_NAME@@
 y vaya desde "Visión general" / "Su cuenta" a la pestaña de "Preferencias".

        URL: {0}

Puede activar/desactivar la notificación para cada sistema si selecciona un
sistema individual desde la "Lista de sistemas". Desde la página individual del
sistema haga clic en la pestaña "Información".

{1}
{2}</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="dailysummary.email.subject">
				<source>@@PRODUCT_NAME@@ Daily Status Report for {0}</source>
				<target>Reporte de estado diario de @@PRODUCT_NAME@@ para {0}</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="dailysummary.email.body">
				<source>This is the @@PRODUCT_NAME@@ Status Report for your account {0}, as of {1}.

This email will be sent when any of the following apply:

1.  The system fails to check in with @@PRODUCT_NAME@@ within a 24-hour window.
2.  The system registers scheduled action activity.

{2}
{3}
Disabling this email:
----------------------

To learn how to disable this email for systems:

https://{4}/rhn/help/reference/en-US/s1-sm-your-rhn.jsp


Thank you for using @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.
{5}
{6}</source>
				<target>Este es el reporte de estado de @@PRODUCT_NAME@@ para su cuenta {0}, {1}.

Este correo-e se enviará cuando uno de los siguientes estados sea
aplicable al sistema específico:

1.  El sistema no se ha registrado con @@PRODUCT_NAME@@ durante un periodo de 24 horas.
2.  El sistema registrado programó una actividad de acción.

{2}
{3}
Desactivando este correo-e:
----------------------

Para aprender a desactivar este correo-e para los sistemas:

https://{4}/rhn/help/reference/en/s1-sm-your-rhn.jsp


Gracias por usar @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.
{5}
{6}</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.verification.notice.body">
				<source>
Dear @@PRODUCT_NAME@@ User,

This email is sent to validate the email address that you have
provided for your Red Hat login. Your Red Hat login, in combination
with an active Red Hat subscription, provides you with access to
systems management capabilities through @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.

To ensure the security of the account information associated with your
Red Hat login, please take a moment to click through the link below
and verify that we have the correct email address. If you do not
confirm your email address, your Red Hat login will eventually be
deactivated.

To confirm your email address, please visit the following URL:

{0}

Thank you for using @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.
{1}
{2}</source>
				<target>
Estimado usuario de @@PRODUCT_NAME@@,

Este correo es enviado con el fin de validar la dirección de correo-e
que usted ha proporcionado para obtener un nombre de usuario de Red Hat.
Su nombre de usuario de Red Hat, junto con una suscripción activa de Red Hat,
le brinda acceso a las funciones de administración de sistemas
a través de @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.

Para garantizar la seguridad de la información de la cuenta asociada
con su nombre de usuario de Red Hat, por favor haga clic en el enlace proporcionado
a continuación y verifique que la información de correo-e sea la correcta.
Si no confirma su dirección de correo-e, su nombre de usuario de Red Hat será
eventualmente desactivado.

 Para confirmar su dirección de correo-e, por favor visite la siguiente URL:

{0}

Gracias por utilizar @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.
{1}
{2}</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.verification.notice.subject">
				<source>Red Hat login Email Verification</source>
				<target>Verificación de correo-e de nombre de usuario de Red Hat</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.verification.warning.body">
				<source>
Dear @@PRODUCT_NAME@@ User,

This email is sent to validate the email address that you have
provided for your Red Hat login. Your Red Hat login, in combination
with an active Red Hat subscription, provides you with access to
systems management capabilities through @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.

To ensure the security of the account information associated with your
Red Hat login, please take a moment to click through the link below
and verify that we have the correct email address. If you do not
confirm your email address, your Red Hat login will eventually be
deactivated.

Please note that this is a final notice.  If you do not click through
this URL within the next 2 days, your Red Hat login will deactivated.

To confirm your email address, please visit the following URL:

{0}

Thank you for using @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.
{1}
{2}</source>
				<target>
Estimado usuario de @@PRODUCT_NAME@@,

Este correo es enviado con el fin de validar la dirección de correo-e
que usted ha proporcionado para obtener un nombre de usuario en Red Hat.
Su nombre de usuario de Red Hat, junto con una suscripción activa de Red Hat,
le brinda acceso a las funciones de administración de sistemas
a través de @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.

Para asegurar la seguridad de la información de la cuenta asociada
con su nombre de usuario de Red Hat, por favor haga clic en el enlace proporcionado
a continuación y verifique que la información de correo-e sea la correcta.
Si no confirma su dirección de correo-e, su nombre de usuario de Red Hat será
al final desactivado.

Por favor observe que este es un aviso final. Si no hace clic en esta URL
en los siguientes dos días, su nombre de usuario de Red Hat será desactivado.

Para confirmar su dirección de correo-e, por favor visite la siguiente URL:

{0}

Gracias por usar @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.
{1}
{2}</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.verification.warning.subject">
				<source>Red Hat Login Email Verification, Final Notice</source>
				<target>Verificación de correo-e de nombre de usuario de Red Hat, último aviso</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.satellitecert.graceperiod.subject">
				<source>Red Hat @@PRODUCT_NAME@@ Server Certificate expiration warning</source>
				<target>Advertencia sobre la expiración del certificado del @@PRODUCT_NAME@@ de Red Hat</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.satellitecert.graceperiod.body">
				<source>
Dear @@PRODUCT_NAME@@ User,

This email is being sent to you to inform you that your @@PRODUCT_NAME@@ Certificate
has expired on your local satellite {0}. After {1} day(s) the systems
management services provided by your @@PRODUCT_NAME@@ Server will become inaccessible.
Please contact your regional Red Hat Customer  Service Representative for information
on how to renew your @@PRODUCT_NAME@@ Certificate.

Thank you for using @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.
--the @@PRODUCT_NAME@@ Team</source>
				<target>
Estimado usuario de @@PRODUCT_NAME@@,

Este correo-e le ha sido enviado para informarle que el certificado de su @@PRODUCT_NAME@@
ha expirado en su satélite local {0}. Dentro de {1} día(s), el servicio de administración
de sistemas proporcionado por su servidor de @@PRODUCT_NAME@@ quedará inaccesible.
hasta que renueve su certificado. Por favor contacte a su representante de servicio al cliente
de Red Hat para obtener información sobre cómo renovar el certificado de su @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.

Gracias por utilizar @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.
--el equipo de @@PRODUCT_NAME@@</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.satellitecert.expired.subject">
				<source>Red Hat satellite certificate expiration notice</source>
				<target>Notificación sobre la expiración del certificado del satélite de Red Hat</target>
			</trans-unit>
			<trans-unit id="email.satellitecert.expired.body">
				<source>
Dear @@PRODUCT_NAME@@ User,

This email is being sent to you to inform you that your @@PRODUCT_NAME@@ Certificate
has expired on your local satellite {0}. The system management services will be inaccessible
until your certificate is renewed. Please contact your regional Red Hat
Customer Service Representative for information on how to renew your @@PRODUCT_NAME@@ Certificate.


Thank you for using @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.
--the @@PRODUCT_NAME@@ Team</source>
				<target>
Estimado usuario de @@PRODUCT_NAME@@,

Este correo-e le ha sido enviado para informarle que el certificado de su @@PRODUCT_NAME@@
ha expirado en su satélite local {0}. El servicio de administración de sistemas será inaccesible
hasta que renueve su certificado. Por favor contacte a su representante de servicio al cliente
de Red Hat para obtener información sobre cómo renovar el certificado de su @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.


Gracias por utilizar @@PRODUCT_NAME@@.
--el equipo de @@PRODUCT_NAME@@</target>
			</trans-unit>
		</body>
	</file>
</xliff>
